<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on @unjello</title>
    <link>http://andrzej.lichnerowicz.pl/en/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on @unjello</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <atom:link href="http://andrzej.lichnerowicz.pl/en/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Deploying a Go Microservice in Kubernetes</title>
      <link>http://andrzej.lichnerowicz.pl/en/blog/deploying_go_microservice_in_k8s/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://andrzej.lichnerowicz.pl/en/blog/deploying_go_microservice_in_k8s/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer Disclaimer: This post will showcase some macOS-specific tools, primarily brew. This isn&amp;rsquo;t to make a platform statement; it&amp;rsquo;s simply to avoid the complexities of multi-platform discussion for brevity&amp;rsquo;s sake.&#xA;Over the Hill and Under the Hill So, this is going to be a bit of a shameless plug, though all the praise towards my current employer, Splunk, is purely accidental :)&#xA;My journey here has been nothing short of remarkable, largely thanks to the incredible people I&amp;rsquo;ve had the chance to work with.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Initial Revision</title>
      <link>http://andrzej.lichnerowicz.pl/en/blog/initial-revision/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://andrzej.lichnerowicz.pl/en/blog/initial-revision/</guid>
      <description>% letter letter: Command not found. % mail To: ^X ^F ^C % help mail help: Command not found. % damn! !: Event unrecognized % logout It&amp;rsquo;s been sort of a tradition, to begin each incarnation of my blog, with a quote from this old joke1. If one can trust the, uh, Internets, this blog was esentially down since 2007. A decade! Enough is enough. Time to get back.&#xA;https://gist.github.com/D3MZ/3915286&amp;#160;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s still the same old story</title>
      <link>http://andrzej.lichnerowicz.pl/en/blog/same_old_story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://andrzej.lichnerowicz.pl/en/blog/same_old_story/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t think I even remember anymore, how many times I have restarted the blog. Last time I wrote something useful, was probably around 2008.&#xA;I still have the old sites backed up somewhere. At least few of them. Unfortunately they&amp;rsquo;re not very useful, mostly because they have been using blogging engines &amp;ndash; either Wordpress-like, or my own &amp;ndash; and while I backed up the code, I did not export anything from the database, leaving myself with just the looks, and no content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One more time?</title>
      <link>http://andrzej.lichnerowicz.pl/en/blog/reboot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://andrzej.lichnerowicz.pl/en/blog/reboot/</guid>
      <description>% /sbin/shutdown -r now It begins to strike me, that I may not be good at blogging. Let&amp;rsquo;s see if I can make it this time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rocking Rust, Git, and GitHub in 2023 Like a Pro</title>
      <link>http://andrzej.lichnerowicz.pl/en/blog/rust_github_2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://andrzej.lichnerowicz.pl/en/blog/rust_github_2023/</guid>
      <description>Falling in Love with SourceHut, But Still Tempted by GitHub Actions SourceHut has recently won my heart with its simplicity and 90&amp;rsquo;s UI vibe, but I can&amp;rsquo;t resist the appeal of GitHub&amp;rsquo;s free workflow automation platform. I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on a few small projects in Python, TypeScript, and Rust, and have set up CI for all of them. Now that I&amp;rsquo;ve revived my blog, I thought I&amp;rsquo;d write about my experience using GitHub Actions for deployment.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
